(Leonard:)That's the definition
of being a know-it-all.
Or in German, a Besserwisser.
(Penny:)How did you think you were
gonna hide your pregnancy?
(Bernadette:)I had a plan-- I kept leaving
Dove Bar wrappers around
(Bernadette:)to explain any weight gain.
(Amy:)Where did you get
empty Dove Bar wrappers?
(Bernadette:)From all the Dove Bars
I ate! I'm pregnant!
Try to keep up!
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
I-I have to go find out
(Bernadette:)if my boss knows.
(Amy:)Well, whatever happens,
we're here for you.
(Bernadette:)Thanks.
You guys are the best.
(Penny:)Yeah, drive safe. We love you.
And give us a call...
(Penny:)Oh, my God,
it was me, it was me!
(Penny:)I'm the one who blabbed
she was pregnant!
What?!
(Penny:)I didn't mean to.
It just slipped out
(Penny:)in front of her assistant
one day. I...
(Bernadette:)I forgot my coat.
Oh! Here's your coat, honey.
(Penny:)That's such a cute jacket.
(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Penny:)God, I feel so bad--
I just lied to her.
(Amy:)Oh, but you did it so well.
That's amazing!
(Amy:)It's like watching a sculptor,
(Amy:)but your clay was lies.
(Penny:)Is that really
what's important right now?